Can I put it in?
入れるかな?
Take a ride.
乗ってごらん
Try making it MG.
MGにしてごらん
Don't gap, just touch.
ギャップしないで、手ついて
Try making it with mango.
マンゴーにしてごらん
Try moving.
動いてごらん
Red
レッ
Hello, today is a lesson.
ス ンだよ、今日はレッスン
Uncle, make yourself comfortable.
おじさん、気持ちよくして
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Growing too much.
成長しすぎる
tight.
きつい
Too intense.
激しすぎる
I've had so much to do today that I've used up all my medicine.
今日いっぱいしちゃって、薬つくしたじゃん
Well then,
じゃあさ、
You can add seeds.
タ ネ付けしていいよ
I guess I can just accept it with my face.
顔で受け止めてもらおうかな
Have you ever had it sprayed on your face?
顔にかけられたことある?
long face
長い顔
I can't choose.
選べない
I'll leave my punishment here for today,
今日の仕置きはここまでにしておくから、
It's disbanded.
解散だね